if she is a free person She decides not
если она свободный человек Она решает не
Her father Not her brother Not her
Её отец Да не брат не
mother Let's talk about the relationship
мама Давайте поговорим об отношениях
between a man and a woman
между мужчиной и женщиной
What an unexpected question Are you sure
[__] неожиданный вопрос Вы уверены
that we need this between Ukra
что нам это нужно между Укра интересно
interesting I wonder what you and let's
Интересно а что вас и давайте так
do it then if we show the cards to me
давайте то уже если вскрывать карты мне
42 to you  how many
42 вам сколько
37 types are real
37 типа реально
Yes, we didn’t, we didn’t leave, yes we didn’t leave, I wanted to run away from you, I
Да мы не не ушли да да не ушли я от вас
didn’t
хотел убежать не убежал Да от вас не
run away, Yes, you can’t run away from you, and what interests you about this in the
убежишь и что вас интересует в этом в
relationship between a man and a
отношениях мужчины и
woman?
женщины
Well, what do you think is
Ну как вы считаете что такое
equality
равноправие
equality? Judging
равноправие Судя
from this word, this is when  subjects have
из этого слова это когда субъекты имеют
equal rights,
равные права
so equal rights, for example, in
так равные права так например вот в
Russia, as I understand it, there are
России я так понимаю что с равноправии
very big problems with equality,
очень большие проблемы
since there are no Well,
так как нет
what do you mean, in your understanding, problems
Ну что значит в вашем понимании проблемы
with equality? Well, for example, I saw
с равноправия Ну вот например я видел
that you have there, for example, in Chechnya, in
что у вас там например в Чечне в
Dagestan, there is something there  It’s
Дагестане есть там что
as if their parents don’t let women out, they
женщин как бы родители не выпускают
forcefully marry them off, but only in
насильно выдают замуж а ну только в
Russia, not Well, for example, in Russia, we
России не Ну вот я например в России у
don’t have that in Ukraine, but that’s how you feel.
нас в Украине нету такого да вот как вы
How do you feel about the fact that in Russia
Как вы относитесь к тому что в России
there is such inequality between men and
есть такое неравноправие мужчины и
women, first of all, there’s a little bit here  It’s not about the
женщины во-первых тут немножко дело не в
country It’s about religion Well, as it is E which is
стране А в религии Ну как есть Э что
higher The Constitution of the Russian Federation
выше Конституция Российской Федерации
or some kind of
или какая-то
religion You know that there are Republics
религия Вы знаете что есть Республики у
that have their own laws No No No
которых есть свои законы Нет Нет Нет
look, the law of the Russian Federation
смотрите закон Российской Федерации
is valid throughout the entire territory of the Russian
действует на всей территории Российской
Federation
Федерации
has The Constitution of the Russian Federation
имеет Конституция Российской Федерации
has the highest  legal force on the
имеет высшую юридическую силу на
territory of the Russian Federation, the wife
территории Российской Федерации жена
who is being held at home will go
которую удерживает дома пойдёт
above her republic and write
выше своей республики и напишет
a statement against the person who is
заявление на человека который его
holding him, she is being held, then
удерживает её удерживает тогда с этим
higher powers will deal with this That is,
будут разбираться вышестоящие силы То
if she runs away from the republic Yes no
есть если она убежит из республики Да
no If this woman sits
нет нет Если эта женщина будет сидеть
at home and thinks about  how bad her
дома и думать о том как же ей плохо
life is, the problem is, you know, the
живётся проблема знаете в чём то
woman is to blame for something. I understand, yes.
виновата женщина Я так понимаю да
And here it’s a little wrong, but how is she to
А тут немножко не так а как винова
blame for this
виноваты в этой
situation? The woman in this situation ca
ситуации женщина в этой в этой ситуации
n’t do anything. Yes, in fact, Well, you
ничего не может сделать Да по сути Ну вы
say she should go where  -
же говорите она должна пойти где-то там
write something there if suddenly she goes
что-то написать если вдруг она пойдёт
higher than her father, brother, matchmaker and other other
выше её отца брата свата и прочего
things, just like look even
прочего прочего также как смотрите даже
with me Here is an example example a girl went
у меня Вот пример пример девочка пошла
higher for example uh at this crossing to
выше например ээ на этом переходе в
Georgia yes like North Ossetia was
Грузию да типа северную осети было в
last year a girl yes from  Dagestan Yes,
прошлом году девушка да из Дагестана Да
she ran away because her brother, her father, was kept
убегала потому что её этот брат отец
locked up and wanted to marry her. Yes, they
держали в заперти хотели выдать замуж Да
beat her, she ran away, she’s
побили её она убежала она
an adult, they detained her, they
совершеннолетняя всё её задержали её
gave her to her father and brother. You know this
отдали отцу и брату Вы знаете эту
story. No, I don’t know. How
историю Нет не знаю А сколько девушке
old was the girl, 20-something already?  who
лет было по там 20 с чем-то уже кто её
gave her, the police detained her, and they
отдал полиция задержала
wrote a statement, that is, a statement,
а они заявление то есть заявление писали
and the lawyer was like, she completely
и адвокат был что типа она совершенно
refuses to return to her
она отказывается чтобы возвращаться к
relatives, she doesn’t want to, they
родственникам она не хочет они её
beat her, look, they returned her
избивают е Посмотрите её вернули всё
anyway, she was given to her relatives by force, she was
равно её отдали родственникам насильно
given to her relatives anyway, but what
всё равно отдали родственникам Да а что
happened in  in a
было в
statement, she stated right here at the
заявлении она прямо вот в этом в на
border station at the
пограничном участке заявляла в отделении
police station that I don’t want to go back, they’re
полиции что я не хочу возвращаться меня
killing me there, they’re beating me, they’ll kill me, she fled
убивают там избивают меня убьют она
to another country, so she didn’t
бежала в другую страну так она не
try to escape to our country
попыталась бежать в нашу страну
somewhere. Let’s say to another city where
куда-нибудь Допустим в другой город где
she can write in
она может написание на своих
she tried to flee her relatives
родственников она попыталась бежать за
abroad. Where she was
границу Где на границе её
caught at the border, they could have thought that she
поймали могли посчитать о том что она
was trying to cross illegally. No, she was absolutely
нелегально пытается пере Нет она
legal, everything was absolutely
легально абсолютно там все абсолютно
legal there, they were absolutely legal with their passports, she had all the
абсолютно легально у неё всё есть
documents, which passports were used to
документы каким паспортам на неё
write an application for her; no one wrote for her.
написано заявление никто не писал на неё
there is no statement the
нет никакого заявления не писали
relatives did not write The relatives
родственники не писали Родственники
came and the forces pulled her out of there gave
приехали и силы её вытащили оттуда дали
a bribe
Там взятку
to someone they found out if uh If there
кому-то они узнали если ээ Если э не
was no statement like that there is no
было заявления вот так нету никакого
statement Look at me now
заявления Посмотрите я вам сейчас
let me tell you a very interesting story
давайте я вам очень интересная история
let's look now now od
давайте сейчас смотрю сейчас од
and so, a native of Dagestan, Patimat
так так вот уроженка Дагестана Патимат
Idrisova, and
Идрисова так
so
вот так с третьего раза
she ran away the third time, she was able to escape the third time, after all, where did
убежала с третьего раза смогла убежать
she run away, in the end, abroad, she
куда она убежала в итоге за границу
ran away somewhere to freedom, look
убежала куда-то на свободу смотрите
And I repeat again, if she had gone
А ещё раз повторяю если бы она уехала
somewhere to another city  and filed an
куда-нибудь в другой город и подала
application for her family, that would have been
заявление на свою семью это было бы
different, she tried to cross the border
другое она пыталась пересечь границу
illegally And how is it legal, absolutely
нелегально А как легально абсолютно
legal, she is an adult, why
легально она взрослый человек почему она
can’t she cross the border, and where did she
не может пересечь границу а куда она
try to cross the border to
пыталась пересечь границу в
Georgia, upper Last, how everyone else moved
Грузию верхний Ласт как и все переезжали
Yes and And how Please explain to me
Да и А каким Объясните мне пожалуйста
how did she
каким образом пешеходным
try to cross the
пешим пешим образом пыталась пересечь
border on foot on foot? Why the hell is it her
границу Нахрена Да это её дело в том-то
business? Freedom is she Why the hell if she could get
дело Свобода она Нахрена если она могла
there by train on the bus because the train wasn’t
туда на поезде на автобусе потому что не
coming then the bus didn’t come then the bus, here she was,
идёт поезд не шли тогда автобус вот она
she arrived and there was a pedestrian crossing Yes there was
она приехала и а и пеший переход Да был
Here it is a pedestrian crossing Yes, what is the problem
Вот она пеший переход Да в чём проблема
through the official point? That is, you are
через официальный пункт То есть вы
now defending a state that
сейчас защищаете государство которое
abuses women,
издевается над женщино
date, I’m trying to
дата на меня наехать я вам пытаюсь
logically
логически
explain to you, you are trying to explain that a
объяснить вы пытаетесь объяснить что
woman does not have the right to travel abroad herself,
женщина не имеет право выехать сама за
why does she have the right, she does not
границу почему она имеет право она не
have the right  it's legal to cross the territory
имеет права легально пересечь территорию
so it's legal, look at it, it's illegal, it's
так легально смотри её ж нелегально она
her, her relatives came like that
Вот её приехали родственники так типа
and they were catching up with her because she was
и они её догоняли потому что она была
locked in a barn. Yes, she was running away from them and they'll
закрыта в сарае Да она убегала от них и
explain it to you. Just
так вот я вам объясню Просто
explain if she hadn't tried to
обясните если бы она не пыталась
cross the territory of another  country,
пересечь территорию другой страны
but if she came to any other city, she
а приехала бы в любой другой город
would write a statement against her
написала бы заявление на своих
relatives that they are holding her by
родственников что они её удерживают
force, why can’t she cross the
силой почему она не может пересечь
border, if she can cross the
границу вот если она может пересечь
borders, she is a free person, why
грани она свободный человек почему
should relatives decide whether to cross the
родственники должны решать пересе
border or not, because they most likely
границу или нет потому нни скорее всего
wrote a statement no no  look, if they
написали заявление нет нет смотри если
wrote a statement, then the police would
бы написали заявление её б тогда полиция
detain her and the police would interrogate her, instead of the
задержала и полиция допрашивать а не
police give her to her relatives, she doesn’t
полиция отдала родственникам не
exist, no, no, auntie, look, you wo
существует нене не тётенька Смотри не ты
n’t divorce me, look, I’ve seen such burnt people
меня не разведёт смотри я таких жжёных
as you have seen and burned more than once,
как ты видел и прожигал ещё не раз
look, if they wrote a statement against her
смотри если бы если бы на неё написали
if there is a crime there,
заявление если там есть состав
they would have detained her, then she would have been
представление её б задержали так её б
arrested Yes, and they wouldn’t have
арестовали Да и родственникам её б не
given her to her relatives no, we don’t have in the Russian
отдали нет у нас нету в Российской
Federation there is no such law that a person is
Федерации нет такого закона что человека
property Yes, they give out to some
как собственность Да выдают каким-то
other people the corpus delicti of a crime, the person
другим людям состав преступления человек
has disappeared without trace. She is an
пропал безвести как безвести Вот она
adult  She says I did
совершеннолетняя Она говорит я никуда не
n’t disappear anywhere. I don’t want a video. There’s a video of her and her
пропадала Всё я не хочу видео есть она с
lawyer. The lawyer says, and this brother and
адвокатом адвокат говорит а этот брат и
him and her husband and mother say that
ему и муж и мама говорят те сечас
now it’s a turning point in general. And so on now you’re defending what the woman,
дальше сейчас защищаешь то что женщина
Yes, and she, you’re starting now, and what is it that
Да а она ты начинаешь сейчас а что это
she crossed?  And what is she like and what did she
она пересекла А что она так а что она
want she she if she is a free
хотела она она если она свободный
person She decides not Her father Yes not her brother
человек Она решает не Её отец Да не брат
nor her mother yes at 20 something years old what should she
ни мама да в 20 с чем-то лет что ей
do yes then why did they take her and
делать да то почему почему её взяли и
give her to her relatives of course she is a
отдали родственникам безусловно она
free person but if  is it
свободный человек но если е
that her parents are
родители ли том что она
missing, they don’t get in touch, they are starting to look for her, let’s say,
пропала не выходит на связь её начинают
no, look,
разыскивать допустим е Нет ещё смотрите
if I write a statement against you, for example,
если я напишу например на вас заявление
that you are missing, so they are looking for you, no,
что вы пропали так вас разыскивают нет
look, your husband, yes, if your husband
смотри вот ваш муж да если ваш муж
wrote a statement that you are missing,
написал заявление что вы пропали
Yes, at the metro station  They check your
Да на станции метро у вас проверяют
documents about You are missing, you say
документы о Вы же пропали вы говорите
No, I’m not missing, everything is fine with me and they
Нет я не пропал со мной всё нормально и
will release you to your husband anyway, they will inform your husband, they will
отпускают мужу всё равно сообщат мужу
inform you, but no one is detaining you
сообщат но вас никто не задерживает
because someone reported that you are
из-за того что кто-то сообщил что вы
missing, we have such a law What is the law
пропали у нас такой закон Какой закон
they're holding Because I'm wanted there's no
держат Потому что я в розыске нету
wanted no no no no rose look
розыска нене не не никакой розы смотри
No this is if as a criminal they can
Нет это если как преступник тебя могут
detain you like this And if for example you if they're
задержать так А если например тебя если
looking for you there as for example a missing person Yes and
там разыскивают как например пропавшего
you're there no one's taking you away won't
Да и ты есть никто тебя не забирает не
arrest you you need to tell me about me
арестует надо рассказывать мне о мо
not A  tell me who by training
не А расскажите вы кто по образованию
I am a lawyer and you and I am a Psychologist And a psychologist
вот Я юрист а вы а я Психолог А психолог
then let me tell you about your
тогда давайте я вам расскажу о ваших
laws because you don’t know them and
законах потому что вы их не знаете да
because no they can’t take a person and
потому что нет не могут человека взять и
detain him because they
задержать из-за того что на него
wrote a statement against him that he  they can’t go missing,
написали заявление что он пропал не
and even more so they can’t give it back. Well,
могут а тем более и не могут отдать Ну
look, they say that the person is missing. It’s
смотрите говорят что человек пропал Это
not a thing, it’s true that they found him. Oh listen, Dude, it’s
же не вещь правда что его нашли О слушай
your suitcase that went missing, come
это Чувак это твой чемодан пропал приедь
take it, it’s true. Wait, who handed it over? By the way, and
забери правда Подождите а кто передал
who handed it over to our authorities or
а кто передал её наши власти или
Georgian yours?  the fact that she did
грузински ваши ваши то что в Грузию она
n’t come to Georgia I just don’t quite
не не приехала Я просто не совсем
understand how she why she
понимаю Каким образом она почему она
crossed the border on foot because I
пешком пересекала границу потому что я
don’t know she wanted to cross they got to
не знаю хотел она пересе доехали до
something there like everyone else from Russia because
чего-то там как и все из России потому
there were a lot of traffic jams like yes When did
что там куча пробок была типа да Когда
it  you had a mobilization that everyone
это у вас была мобилизация что все
fled to Georgia Yes, uh, breakneck Yes,
бежали в Грузию Да ээ сломя ноги Да там
everything was so packed there, both buses and
было всё короче забито так и автобусы и
cars Yes, that’s why I get to some
машины Да поэтому Доезжаю до какого-то
point there and walked On foot, that’s her business, on foot on a
там пункта и шли Пешком это её дела
bicycle, she’s a free
пешком на велосипеде она свободный
person, you don’t owe yours  slurped
человек вам вас не должно ваше хлебало
Yes, she shouldn’t be interested in why she had to
Да не должно интересоваться зачем ей
walk since she is a free person.
было пешком так она свободный человек
She decides
Она решает
to walk through the airport through any
пешком через аэропорт чере любым
legal way if it allows,
легальным способом если это позволяет
she wants to walk. What difference does it make to you
она хочет пешком Какая вам разница
why it was her? That is, you begin to
почему это она То есть вы начинаете
justify these animals Yes, justify
оправдывать этих зверей Да оправдывать
You are looking for You are looking for Why the victim did
Вы ищете Вы ищете Почему жертва сделала
so why did the victim do this you
так А почему жертва сделала так вы
justify the rapist you justify the
оправдываете насильника вы оправдайте
rapist yes you took the side of the
насильника да вы встали на сторону
tyrant you are not a psychologist you are not a
тирана вы не психолог вы не
psychologist you are not a
психолог вы не
psychologist crazy understand you are crazy for real
психолог псих понимаете вы псих реально
You
Вы
really are always This is such a
реально всегда Вот это есть такая
Russian Theme yes you are always for the one who is
Российская Тема да вы всегда за того кто
the tyrant Who humiliates  destroys mocks
тиран Кто унижает уничтожает издевается
This is Russian psychology
Вот это есть Российская психология
because I'll tell you yes And if
потому что я я тебе скажу да И если бы
you were running away yes And I want you to
ты убегала да А я хочу чтобы э ты
feel what this girl felt Yes, I
ощутила то что эта девушка ощущала Да я
really would like to see on the news
вот вот реально хотел бы в новостях
How are you?  and
посмотреть Да как тебя там какие-то лу и
I will And what is it that she decided not to
я буду А что это она решила не в
go to the Yaroslavl region Ache She
Ярославскую область выехать Аче Она
decided to go abroad Yes why Yes why
решила за границу Да почему Да почему
Sashenka Snezhnaya Yes, so Lamana is shorter
Сашенька Снежная Да так ламану короче
through Upper Lars Well, why do you know and you
через Верхний Ларс Ну почему зна а
know what the difference is between me and you
знаешь в чём разница между мной и тобой
but in general I don’t care What’s the difference here  you and I are having a
а вообще пофиг В чём разница вот у нас с
monologue and not a
тобой монолог а не
dialogue, and why do you want to complain about
диалог и что ты хочешь пожаловаться об
this? no, I would just like it, well, if not
этом нет мне просто бы ну так если не
no, look, if
нет смотри если не хочешь пожаловаться
you don’t want to complain, then shut up. Listen to an intelligent person. It’s given to me to listen to you. So you’re already listening.
мне тебя слушать Так ты же уже слушаешь
Look, you’re listening and now you’re talking.
Смотри ты слушаешь а теперь говоришь
[ __ ] it.  Look, I’ll tell you as a psychologist Yes,
Нахрена Смотри я как психолог тебе скажу
I’m completely manipulating you Yes, you
Да я полностью тобой манипулирую Да ты
say I don’t want to listen to you, but you
говоришь не хочу тебя слушать но
listen, you see Why Because I’m a
слушаешь видишь Почему Потому что я
real psychologist You have a diploma in
настоящий психолог У тебя есть диплом по
psychology,
психологии
bought, I like you, yes, because I’m
купленный я нравлюсь да потому что я
luring
сманить
you in, I’m a pretty boy I know Yes, I have
тобой я симпатичны мальчик Я знаю Да у
There is charisma, yes, I am drawn to it, Yes,
меня Харизма есть да я затягивают им Да
and you flow, you float,
и ты течёшь ты плывёшь
yes. There is a very interesting timbre of the voice; it
да Очень интересный тембр голоса есть он
wheezes a little more. Yes, it’s so that you get high too, really,
захрип ещё немножко Да это так что и ты
yes. But I won’t give you a damn. You see,
правда да Но я тебе не дам блин Видишь
for several reasons, including
по нескольким причинам в том числе
Because you are Russian and in  Tom
Потому что ты Россиянка а в том Потому
Because you have a complete relationship with a
что ты у тебя конченное отношение к
woman they
женщина
will convince
убедят
Yes, most likely You know why
Да скорее всего А знаешь почему Понятия
I have no idea Childhood trauma, maybe yes the
не имею детская травма может быть да
stahl are not closed Yes, what did you have in
шталь не закрыты Да что у тебя было в
childhood? Tell me now, we’ll figure it out, I’d rather
детстве расскажи сейчас разберём я лучше
not know about it. Let me do it
об этого об этом не знать Давай я могу
now.  I can, as a psychologist, you’re not there, I’m not
сейчас я могу как психолог тебя нет я не
ready to talk about it
готова об этом рассказывать в прямом
live, but I can tell you one thing, there
эфире Но я могу тебе сказать одну вещь
was violence. Yes, in our country it’s
насилие было Да у нас в стране
really better not to be a victim, that’s
действительно лучше жертвой не быть это
the way it is, and not even because the
так и есть и даже не потому что тебя
authorities don’t support you, but because  People have a reason to
власть не поддерживает а потому что тебя
starve you. You see, you, as a part of this
морить Вот видите Вы как частичка этого
people, already screw this girl, you I didn’t I
народа уже чмыри эту девушку вы я не Я
tried to understand I tried look no
пыталась понять Я пыталась смотрите нет
you’re not listening you’re not I’m not listening because
вы не слушаешь вы не я не слушаю потому
look I already understand your psycho you
что смотри я понимаю уже твою психо ты
want you you 10 reasons  why
хочешь ты ты 10 каких-то доводов почему
didn’t you say why he didn’t give reasons I
она ты не говорила почему он не доводы я
asked you questions you
вопросы задавала ты мне ты почему то
asked me for some reason, that is, you were looking for her guilt somewhere Why
есть ты искала где-то вину её А почему
so Why so I didn’t
так А почему так Я не искала искала
look for it
искала искала искала Правда Ну да да Ну
I didn’t look for it  I
признайся Нет я не искала её вину Я
tried to find out from you why this
пыталась у тебя выяснить почему так
happened and where you are, I just
произошло и где ты это у я просто этого
didn’t see it, look at it, I
не видела есть посмотришь Посмотришь по
can tell you that it’s the same
те сказать могу тебе сказать да так и
in our country, if you’re a victim, you’d
есть у нас в стране если ты жертва тебе
better not live. You’ll still be worse
лучше не жить Ты всё равно будешь хуже
than that
чем тот
maniac.  but by the way, this is not only in our
маньяк но это кстати не только у нас в
country. Where else is there
стране А где ещё
such a thing? Yes, a lot. Where where. Well,
такое Да много Где где Ну вот
look. Yesterday
смотри Вчера
I literally watched
буквально я смотрела
a video about Natasha
ролик про Наташу
Kampusch, you know what she is? I have no idea,
кампуш знаешь что это такая Понятия не
this is a Norwegian victim who
имею это норвежская жертва которая 10
was there for 10 years from 8 years old to 18 years old, she was in  captivity of a
лет была с 8 лет до 18 она была в плену
sexual maniac and when she turned
сексуального маньяка и когда исполнилось
18, he took her to a ski
18 он её вывез на горнолыжный
resort and she went to the toilet and She
курорт и ей она пошла в туалет и Ей
managed to meet people and tell them
удалось встретить людей и сказать им о
that help, I am Natasha Kampusch, I am in
том что помогите я Наташа кампуш я в
captivity, she told them this, they
плену нахожусь она им это говорила они
seemed
казались
Russian, so in the
русскими так вот в
comments it was  it was said that
комментариях было высказано о том что
the Russians, as always, in general, all the
русские как всегда в общем все
comments were about
комментарии были о
the Russians.
русских
Yes, and I wrote a comment, you know what
Да и я написала комментарий знаешь какой
kind. Thank God that there were
какой Слава Богу что там оказались
Russians there, otherwise we would have to
русские а то пришлось бы о маньяке
talk about a maniac who held a girl in
говорить который 10 лет держал девочку в
sexual
сексуальном
captivity for 10 years. And so he, too, could be Russian
плену А так он тоже мог быть русский
Maybe with this there are no good ones and no
Может с онто дело нету хороших и нет
bad ones the
плохих
maniac was Russian Yes, of course not And
маньяк был русский Да нет конечно А
how do you know what the name of the
откуда ты знаешь как звали
maniac was? So look at the story Natasha is a Russian Norwegian a Russian native of Russia What was
маньяка Так посмотри историю Наташ
his name Naturally he is
России Как его звали Естественно он
Ukrainian not Russian Russian you definitely
украинец не русский русский однозначно
see Russian these Russian bastards are everywhere
видишь русский эти [__] русские всюду
shorter than nasty stuff  do Yes, you're very
короче гадости делают Да ты очень
cool I'm awesome, the coolest guy from
классный Я офигенный самый охуенный из
Ukraine I really
Украины
like yes But in short I You
парнишка Мне очень нравится да Но короче
know I'm like a forbidden fruit for you
я Знаешь я для тебя как запретный плод
you won't bite me You know I
ты меня не укусишь Ты знаешь я меня
'll be Ukrainian girls ku everything is
будут украинские девчонки ку всё
broken That's how we are Ukrainian guys
обломалась Вот так мы украински хлопци
for Ukrainian girls And you  sit
для украинских девчат А вы сидить
threaten your lips in short twitch your legs
грозить собе губы короче дёргает ноги
lift up Ukrainians are the most beautiful whoever I say Like it,
поднимаете Украинки найкраще хто це
leave a comment and
твержу Ставьте лайк лишайте комент и
subscribe Glory to Ukraine
подписуйтесь Слава украини
Write to my Telegram directly at once axis VN
Пиши на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more
апок це дуже и дуже
respectfully
важливо